twomenandatruck.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy | TWO MEN AND A TRUCK

**Last updated: December 11, 2019**

The purpose of this website is to provide visitors with useful information and allow them the opportunity to request additional information regarding moving/relocation needs. Our visitors have the right to be aware of any information collected and used, and under what circumstances, if any, information is disclosed.

## GENERAL PRIVACY AND DATA RESPONSIBILITY

TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® does not sell or share information collected about you or the services you are requesting. Any information collected, regarding you or the services requested, will only be used to provide information or perform the services requested. We thoroughly vet any third-party services we utilize to ensure they will treat your information with the respect you deserve.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

Registration is not required to enter our site.

We respect each website visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this privacy policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.

For each visitor to our website, the web server automatically recognizes the visitor's domain name only; it does not recognize email addresses and does not uniquely identify the individual or other identifiable details. The information we collect is used for internal review and to improve or enhance our website’s content. Under no circumstances is data shared with third-party organizations for commercial purposes.

Individuals may choose to submit either estimate request forms or customer service inquiry forms. During completion of these forms, users must include certain contact information. This information is never sold or shared with any third-party organizations. It is gathered only for the purposes of contacting visitors regarding services for which interest has been expressed. The information individuals submit will be shared with the franchise location that the individual chooses from our list of franchise locations.

We do not have an order form. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information collected from our website.

From time to time, we engage our visitors through online surveys. On these occasions, we do not sell or share our subscribers’ email addresses.

### NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

We reserve the right to revise our privacy policy at any time without advance notice. Any change to this policy will be posted on this site and the new policy will apply only to information collected following the posting of the new policy.

### MOVE QUOTE FORM INFORMATION

We provide visitors to our website with the ability to enter their move details and personal information to initiate a quote for our services. We store this information, both in your browser while you complete the form and in our internal systems after submission, and use it to estimate and provide services. The information stored in your browser is stored for the purpose of improving your experience while interacting with our web form by having the ability to recall specific information when choosing to go back and edit information before submitting. By entering your information, you are willingly sharing personal information with us to be used as referenced in the General Privacy and Data Responsibility section of this policy. Once the form is completed and submitted, all information stored in your browser is automatically cleared. Your local storage can also be cleared at any time through your browser settings.

### CHAT FEATURE

TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® processes and stores personal data within the online chat feature for the purpose of providing support via chat. You have the right to request your personal information collected be deleted, and you may obtain a copy of any personal data stored in the chat database by contacting us via the steps outlined in the DELETING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION section of this policy.

### EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS

By providing your contact and other information to TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® or through this Site, you have given your express consent for TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® and its franchisees to use your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Notice. To the extent that applicable law requires express consent, express written consent, or “opt-in” for the collection and use of certain types of personal information, TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® will maintain processes and procedures to ensure such information is collected with express consent. Each communication that potential customers receive from TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® will give instructions on opting out or unsubscribing from future email communications.

### SECURITY AND SAFEGUARDS

The security of your information is very important to TWO MEN AND A TRUCK®. TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® uses appropriate administrative, technical, personnel, and physical safeguards to protect the security of your personal information. TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® also makes all attempts to ensure only necessary people and third parties have access to personal information in order to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and unauthorized use or modification. TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® uses some of the most advanced Internet security technology available today to protect your information. TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® practices industry standards and frameworks for securing data systems and the data that is stored.

### TRACKING AND STORAGE OF INFORMATION

If you choose to opt-in to our tracking policy displayed on every page of our website, we will utilize cookies to enhance the user experience while on our site. This includes the use of location selection cookies to eliminate the requirement of subsequent selection when returning or viewing apps or other pages of the website. Remarketing/retargeting cookies are also utilized to display advertisements on other third-party websites based on visits. All remarketing/retargeting tracking abides by guidelines outlined with that specific ad provider network. A session value is assigned while visiting a webpage to remember events or actions you have completed while on the site. This value is updated upon any subsequent visits. IP addresses tracked through Google Analytics are anonymized, per Google guidelines.

Cookies strictly necessary for site functionality are those utilized to track a user’s opt-in status for the purpose of recording consent, selected location information from the last visited page to keep your desired location set and the user’s browser language to keep your preferred or selected content language in place across the website.

If you opted into our tracking policy, but still wish to clear remarketing/retargeting pixels, these may be removed by following the instructions for cookie deletion for your specific web browser.

### DELETING OR REQUESTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

In ordinance with European Union GDPR guidelines and the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), Personal Identifiable Information (PII) that is stored can be deleted or obtained per request by filling out this form; sending an email to [dataadmin@twomen.com](mailto:dataadmin@twomen.com) and providing your name, address and phone number; or calling us at 844-276-9863. The request will be fulfilled within 30 days after any transactions pending with TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® have ended, including outstanding damage claims, pending moves, and/or outstanding payment. The request will include removal of personal information including Name, Email Address, and Phone Number from all internal systems.

### CALL TRACKING

Call tracking is utilized to display dynamic phone numbers across our website. These help to identify the source that helped you find our website. Calls may be recorded for training purposes and any personal identifiable information is redacted within the recorded call file when possible. The information you provide on the call will not be sold to a third- party, but the call will be stored with our third-party vendor.

### EXTERNAL LINKS

TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any external websites to which it links to from this site. These other websites may collect their own cookies and data from users or solicit personally identifiable information that is beyond our control. You should consult each website’s privacy policy or contact the website administrators directly if you have any questions about use of the information they may be collecting.

### NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

We reserve the right to revise our privacy policy at any time without advance notice. Any change to this policy will be posted on this site and the new policy will apply only to information collected following the posting of the new policy.

### CONFLICT RESOLUTION

We are committed to resolving disputes within five (5) business days. If problems arise, visitors may contact us by mail, email, telephone or fax.

### WEBSITE ADMINISTRATION/CONTACT INFORMATION

**Business name:**  TWO MEN AND A TRUCK®/INTERNATIONAL, Inc.   
 **Address:**  3400 Belle Chase Way   
 **City:**  Lansing   
 **State/Province:**  MI   
 **ZIP:**  48911   
 **Country:**  USA   
 **Phone:**  1-800-345-1070   
 **Fax:**  517-394-7432   
 **Website URL:**  https://www.twomenandatruck.com   
 **Website e-mail:**  webmaster@twomenandatruck.com

## Mini Mover Mania Game Privacy Policy

TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® (“ ** _Two Men_** ”, “ ** _we_** ”, “ ** _us_** ”, or “ ** _our_** ”) is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you may provide us through your mobile device (e.g., iPhone, iPad, iPod touch, Android device) when using the Mini Movers Mania game (“ ** _Mini Mover Mania_** ” or the “ ** _Application_** ”). This Privacy Policy informs you of our privacy practices in relation to data gathered through the use of the Application. The terms of this Privacy Policy apply to all users of the Application. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease the use of the Application.

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected through the Application. If you have any questions about how your data or personally identifiable information is gathered through the TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® website, then please see our website Privacy Policy [here.](https://twomenandatruck.com/privacy-policy#privpolicy)

_Information Collection_. Mini Mover Mania does not collect any personal identifiable information about you. However, we may collect non-personal and non-identifiable technical data and related information (“ ** _Analytical Information_** ”) about your use of the Application.

_Use of Information Collected_. TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® may use the Analytical Information we collect for any of the following purposes: (i) to understand how users use the Application; (ii) to make improvements to the Application; (iii) to provide user support or respond to specific requests from users; (iv) to protect the security or integrity of the Application; (v) to comply with legal, regulatory, and other good governance obligation; and (vi) where necessary as part of any restructuring or sale of TWO MEN AND A TRUCK®'s assets.

_Sharing of Information Collected_. TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® may share the information we collect upon lawful request by government authorities, law enforcement, and regulatory authorities where required or permitted by law and/or for tax or other purposes. Subject to applicable law, information may also be released to external parties in response to legal process, and when required to comply with laws, or to enforce our agreements, corporate policies, and/or terms of use or supply, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of TWO MEN AND A TRUCK®. In addition, we may disclose information to prospective or actual buyers in the event that TWO MEN AND A TRUCK® sells all or any of its business or assets.

_Children’s Privacy_. We do not collect personal information from children under thirteen (13) years of age through the Application. If you are younger than eighteen (18) years of age, you may use Mini Mover Mania only with the permission and involvement of your parent(s) or guardian.

_Changes to this Privacy Policy_. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page in order to reflect changes in the law and/or our privacy practices. We will update the date at the top of the Privacy Policy accordingly. Subject to any other requirements of applicable law, by downloading or using the Application you consent to the use and processing of the information as described in this Privacy Policy (as amended from time to time).

_Contact_. If you have any further questions concerning this Privacy Policy and the use of data related to the Application, please contact [Games@twomen.com](mailto:Games@twomen.com).
